hello everybody we are the fine brothers
大家好，我们是好兄弟
it is possible that some of you don't
有些人可能不会
know who we are but we are the founders
知道我们是谁，但我们是创始人
of FB we can say it together hi we're
的FB我们可以一起说，嗨，我们是 五
the five brothers I don't know why we
这五兄弟我不知道我们为什么
don't consider yourselves warned
不要考虑你自己的警告
anymore okay not gonna spoil things
再好吧，不会破坏的东西
except for this update video that has a
除了这个更新视频有一个
lot of things that we're giving you an
很多我们给你的东西
update about so this is an update video
更新关于这是一个更新视频
we're gonna have to be doing these a
我们将不得不做这些
little bit more as a channel like ours
更像我们这样的渠道
that has so many different shows on it
它有很多不同的节目
there's changes that happen and it can
有可能发生的变化
be confusing if we don't talk to you
如果我们不和你说话，我们会感到困惑
guys so this is the first of probably
所以这可能是第一个
many whether it's our other team members
很多人是否是我们其他的团队成员
here that will be coming on to kind of
这里将会出现这种情况
give you the general update but this is
给你一般的更新，但这是
about gaming yeah Gaming update so we've
关于游戏是啊游戏更新，所以我们已经
done a lot of updates about gaming over
做了很多关于游戏的更新
time because it is the thing on the
时间，因为它是关于事物的
channel that is uh that struggles the
这是呃那个挣扎的频道
most because only certain people like to
最因为只有某些人喜欢
watch it on the channel and so even
在频道上观看，甚至是
right now it's yet another update about
现在这是另一个更新
how we're having to change the way
我们如何改变方式
gaming works on the react channel so
游戏就这样在反应频道上运作
first of all the Tuesday game is the one
首先是周二的比赛 三十
off games those aren't going anywhere
那些不在任何地方的游戏
this is all about the Let's Plays
这是关于Let's Plays的
playing a game all the way through that
通过这一切玩游戏
we brought back several months ago after
我们几个月前带回来了
a lot of clamor for it because we know
因为我们知道，所以大声疾呼
how much the people who watch that
观看那些人的人数
content probably are more obsessed with
内容可能更痴迷于
those videos in any other video that FB
FB中的任何其他视频中的这些视频
even makes is the less play fans just
甚至使得球迷只是玩球迷而已
like as obsessed as we are here at the
就像我们在这里的痴迷一样
company about them we love them a lot
关于他们的公司我们非常爱他们
but it's the struggle of not everybody
但这不是每个人的斗争
wants to watch those so here's reality
希望看到这些是现实
check time yeah so the reality is that
检查时间耶，所以现实是这样的
even in the other update videos we
即使在其他更新视频我们
talked about it the gaming episodes are
谈到它的游戏情节
some of the most expensive things that
一些最昂贵的东西
we produce with the amount of time that
我们产生的时间量
it takes to put them together and so
它需要把它们放在一起等等
we've always been trying to figure out
我们一直在试图弄清楚
well how do we get more people to watch
以及我们如何让更多的人观看
them and how do we make this work but
他们和我们如何做这项工作，但
the time that goes into having all the
所有的时间
talented and the producer months
有才华和生产者月份
literally everything if you just aren't
从字面上看，一切如果你不是
there because that has happening we're
因为那是我们正在发生的事情
having to make a bit of a change because
不得不做出一点改变，因为
it's not just impacting like the Let's
它不只是像Let's那样影响
Plays themselves it actually is
实际上是自己玩
impacting the channel completely this is
完全影响频道这是
the wonderful algorithm problems on
奇妙的算法问题
YouTube ongoing where if you end up
YouTube继续在哪里，如果你最终
having a video on your channel or a show
在您的频道或节目上播放视频
that we make that is getting less views
我们认为这是越来越少的意见
then that makes all the other shows on a
那么这使得所有其他节目
channel also start to get less views as
频道也开始获得较少的观点
well because it stops recommending the
以及因为它停止推荐
videos out to you if you don't watch the
视频给你，如果你不看
gaming episodes yeah that's why you
游戏情节是啊，这就是为什么你
might realize if you stopped watching
可能会意识到如果你停止观看
one of your favorite youtubers for like
你最喜欢的YouTube用户之一
a week and then you'd like never get
一个星期，然后你永远不会得到
recommended their video again because
因为再次推荐他们的视频
that's kind of the way the algorithm is
这就是算法的方式
we are talking to YouTube about this
我们正在与YouTube谈这件事
they don't believe us all the time about
他们一直不相信我们
these things so the Let's Plays though
这些东西，所以让我们玩
are not complete
不完整
we know away forever they're just
我们永远知道他们只是
leaving YouTube readapt we adapt and
让我们适应并适应YouTube
change Roth what's happened to the Let's
改变罗斯发生了什么事让我们
Plays we're gonna be moving and
我们将会移动和播放
transitioning a lot of what we do when
过渡了很多我们在什么时候做的事情
it comes to gaming over to twitch we're
它涉及到游戏结束我们的抽搐
gonna be doing a lot of other things on
会做很多其他的事情
Twitch and I've already started playing
Twitch和我已经开始玩了
around with twitch and so this is
抽搐周围，所以这是
telling you all the different things
告诉你所有不同的事情
we're gonna be doing on Twitch and going
我们会在Twitch上做并继续
to twitch is to help make this more
抽搐是为了帮助更多
sustainable because we're live we don't
因为我们活着，所以我们不能
have to worry as much about things like
不得不担心类似的事情
the editing we're able to also do things
编辑我们也可以做的事情
that we see comments about all the time
我们总是看到评论
probably two most common comments from
大概有两个最常见的评论
the gaming fans are why aren't you
游戏迷们为什么不是你
finishing this game a hell of a lot
完成这个游戏很多地狱
faster and it's well it's just a year to
更快，这是好的，这只是一年
play a game correct yes and also a lot
玩一个游戏是正确的，也是很多
of times we'll play a game and then
我们会玩游戏，然后玩
people will say that was awesome played
人们会说这真的很棒
with another generation but it's not
与另一代，但它不是
gonna work right so this is gonna kind
会正确工作，所以这会很好
of kill two birds with one stone as they
一箭双雕
say make it more sustainable to produce
说让它更可持续地生产
and also be able to do both of those
也能够做到这一点
things on Twitch and more easy way and
Twitch上的东西，更简单的方法和
even we'll talk about a little later
即使我们稍后再谈
which is that the hope is because the
这是希望是因为
money on YouTube with D monetization and
在YouTube上与D货币化和
all the problems with the views twitch
观点抽搐的所有问题
is hopefully a different solution that
希望是一个不同的解决方案
allows you guys to help support the show
让你们帮助支持这个节目
more to help us continue to make it with
更多的是帮助我们继续做到
subscribing and donating and things like
订阅和捐赠等等
that so let's roll through specifically
那就让我们特别介绍一下
like yeah what is the transition going
喜欢是什么过渡去了
to be from the Let's Plays on YouTube to
从Let's在YouTube上播放到
now all this content on Twitch so first
现在Twitch上的所有内容都是如此
is that with until dawn that is going to
直到黎明即将到来
wrap up tomorrow last let's play upload
我们明天最后一次打包上传
tomorrow on the react channel
明天在反应频道
Benny is gonna cry bet he's a crier I
本尼会哭泣，他打赌他是一个蹩脚的人
don't know if you know that it's a very
不知道你是否知道这是一个非常
gonna try not to cry yet I've not but if
要尽量不要哭但我没有，但如果
I was gonna say it's a known thing but I
我会说这是一件已知的事情，但我
think it's only known to the people who
认为这只是人们所知道的
work here that I cry out so tomorrow
在这里工作，我明天就这样哭泣
until dawn is finishing on the channel
直到黎明在通道上完成
and then next week on Thursday is going
然后下周星期四即将开始
to be bringing Tom Tori and Scott who
带来汤姆托里和斯科特谁
have been playing until dawn this whole
一直玩到凌晨这整个
time they're going to be completing the
时间他们将完成
until dawn experience live on Twitch
直到黎明经历住在Twitch
with the VR prequel and that's going to
与VR前传，这将是
be next week on Thursday that you'll be
下周星期四你会
able to do that so if you want to see
能够做到这一点，如果你想看到
the last until dawn with those people
与那些人在一起的最后一天
you're gonna have to go to twitch see
你将不得不去抽搐看看
that's how we're trying to get you to go
这就是我们如何努力让你走
over there we're not you have to go so
在那边我们不是必须这样
next is that the two games everybody's
其次是大家的两场比赛
been asking for the most over the past
过去一直在追求最多
while it's doki-doki literature Club and
而它是doki-doki文学俱乐部和
dream daddy
梦中的爸爸
so first week of April we're gonna start
所以四月的第一周我们会开始
playing those yes but it'll be doki-doki
打那些是的，但它会是doki-doki
first then dream daddy but that's going
首先，然后梦想爸爸，但这是事实
to be multi-generational it's going to
这将是多代的
be
是
multiple our streams again getting
多个我们的流再次获得
through these games substantially faster
通过这些游戏大大加快
potentially in just two to three weeks
可能只有两到三周
and that for us that's always been that
对我们来说，那一直是这样
extra layering of what we can do here
我们可以在这里做的额外分层
with having so many generations I think
我觉得有这么多代人
it'll be really interesting to watch
观看会非常有趣
every week as they're progressing
每周都在进行
through the game what are the different
通过游戏有什么不同
choices and the different things that
选择和不同的事情
the teens are experiencing and thinking
青少年正在经历和思考
versus the elders and you can watch that
与长辈相比，你可以观看
week by week now which is cool we're
现在每周一周，这是很酷的我们
hoping a few weeks after we launch Let's
希望在我们推出Let's后数周
Plays on Twitch to actually start doing
在Twitch上玩真的开始做
weekly generational gaming tournaments
每周世代游戏锦标赛
but what we've always wanted to do but
但是我们一直想要做的，但是
have not really been able to do on
还没有真正做到
YouTube is have the generational
YouTube有世代
tournaments all in the same game
锦标赛全部在同一场比赛中
multiple weeks like each week a
多周像每周a
different generation then the winners of
不同的一代，然后是赢家
each play in the grand react
每个人都扮演盛大的反应
generational championship tournament
世代锦标赛
very moderate it's very important
非常温和这是非常重要的
there's talk of that becoming a Sunday
有关于成为星期天的谈话
stream so that's coming but that's still
流，所以即将到来，但仍然是
not all because as we continue to grow
不是全部，因为我们继续增长
in hopeful success of this initiative on
希望这一倡议取得成功
Twitch we also want to kind of look at
抽搐我们也想看看
the shows that are very popular on
这些节目非常受欢迎
YouTube that everyone loves to play
YouTube，每个人都喜欢玩
along with and figure out the live
随着并找出现场
version of that so we're talking about
我们正在谈论的版本
things like guess that song or try not
比如猜这首歌或者尝试不做
to laugh and trying to do those things
笑，并试图做这些事情
not just live but also with you guys in
不只是活着，还会和你们在一起
the chat playing along or sending things
聊天玩或者发送东西
as we're going to try to stop everybody
因为我们将试图阻止每个人
I think we're trying to figure out of
我想我们正在努力解决
like some of these shows might work well
像这些节目中的一些可能运作良好
to be an hour long two-hour long live
长达一个小时的长达两小时的长时间的生活
version of it and they're very engaging
它的版本，他们非常有吸引力
with you guys and have fun in that way
和你们一起玩这种方式
but it also could be that we have some
但也可能是我们有一些
things that are showing almost behind
几乎落后的东西
the scenes of right doing these things
正确地做这些事情的场景
like challenge chalice is a good example
挑战圣杯就是一个很好的例子
of like we could kind of maybe show that
像我们可能会显示的那样
while we're filming or you can just
而我们正在拍摄，或者你可以
watch the filming of a teens react we're
观看青少年的拍摄反应我们
trying to figure out all these different
试图弄清楚所有这些不同
things that you guys can help us figure
你们可以帮助我们的东西
out what do you like what do you don't
你喜欢什么，你不喜欢什么
so all of that wasn't enough to get you
所以这一切都不足以帮助你
to follow us over on Twitch and
跟随我们在Twitch和
subscribe and donate if you're able to
订阅并捐赠，如果你能够
help support and make us be able to keep
帮助支持并使我们能够保持
making all this stuff the community team
使所有这些东西成为社区团队
is gonna still be streaming over there
将仍然在那里流
they've been streaming there for a while
他们已经在那里流了一段时间
now they're gonna be hanging out playing
现在他们会在外面玩
games all the time so there's gonna be
所有的时候都会有游戏
streams constantly but including Tom and
不断流，但包括汤姆和
Eric streaming on Tuesdays and fortnight
Eric星期二和两周播出
Fridays with Tori so that's gonna be
星期五与托里，所以这将是
going all the time it's gonna be streams
一直往前走，这将是流
multiple hours basically every single
基本上每个小时多个小时
day which is pretty awesome so to kind
这真是太棒了
of wrap up this whole update video is
包括这整个更新视频是
that we're having to figure out how to
我们必须弄清楚如何
evolve as an experiment yeah and that
作为一个实验演化是的
the reality of it is for the company
它的现实是针对公司的
overall is that we're making like 20
总的来说，我们制作的像20
videos a week now you guys are loving
现在你们都爱上一周的视频
the watcher we're loving
我们很爱的观察者
but it's a struggle to figure out how to
但如何解决这个问题还很困难
actually make enough money to keep
实际上赚够了钱
producing those especially when you have
尤其是当你有这些产品时
a team as large as this team has become
一支和这支球队一样大的球队
and so that's where you end up in a
所以这就是你最终成为的地方
situation from YouTube D monetizing and
YouTube D货币化和收益的情况
YouTube not serving the videos out to
YouTube未将视频提供给
the fans you have to start bringing the
你必须开始带球迷
content on YouTube and it makes a very
在YouTube上的内容，它使得非常
little bit amount of money then you end
那么你的一点点钱就结束了
up on Facebook and you make a little bit
在Facebook上，你做了一点点
of money and now you're trying to go
的钱，现在你正在努力去
over to twitch to try to make a little
过度抽搐尝试做一点点
bit of money because it just hasn't the
有点钱，因为它只是没有
industry hasn't matured yet where the
行业还没有成熟的地方
things like advertising just pays for it
像广告这样的东西只是为了付钱
all and that's why you'll see us or some
所有这就是为什么你会看到我们或一些
other channels end up with things like
其他渠道最终会出现类似情况
subscribe on Twitch donate on Twitch
在Twitch上订阅Twitch捐赠
even though it feels like but you have
即使它感觉像但你有
this huge YouTube channel what do you
这个巨大的YouTube频道你是什么
need that for and it is the reality that
需要这样做，这是现实
the team that is here is producing so
这里的团队正在生产
much content we can't do some of these
很多内容我们无法做到这些
things unless we have some of that
除非我们有一些这样的东西
support so if you are able to subscribe
支持，所以如果你能订阅
it is really a huge huge thing that you
这真的是一个巨大的事情，你
can do to support FBE there's of course
当然可以做到支持FBE
all of the usual twitch perks when you
所有通常的抽搐特技当你
subscribe like this sub only discord and
订阅像这个分歧只是不和谐
ads free and emotes and all that so all
广告自由和表达，所有这一切
that is already there there's gonna be
那已经是那里了
even more cool stuff especially in
更特别是更酷的东西
success as we keep rolling this out and
我们一直在努力实现成功
seeing what everybody wants but we're
看到每个人都想要什么，但我们是
really excited about this move to twitch
真的很兴奋这个抽动的举动
to engage with you all even in a whole
甚至在整体上与所有人进行交流
new way we just appreciate you rolling
新的方式，我们只是感谢你滚动
with the punches with us and trying to
与我们一起拳击并尝试着
figure out how to make this all work and
弄清楚如何使这一切工作和
won't be keeping on going with these
将不会继续与这些
types of update videos so come on back
更新视频的类型如此回来
help you guys know more of what's going
帮助你们知道更多的事情
on why we're changing what we're
为什么我们要改变我们的
changing because the Albert observe this
因为阿尔伯特观察到了这一点
video to you help everyone else
视频给你帮助其他人
understand doubtful when they're like
当他们喜欢时，理解可疑
what happened to Let's Plays you guys
发生了什么让我们玩你们
can all tell I predict 130.000 views I
都可以告诉我预测130.000的意见我
predict a hundred and seventy thousand
预计十七万
he really likes the algorithm he thinks
他非常喜欢他认为的算法
that it works thank you so much again we
它的作品非常感谢你我们
will see you next week
下周将会见到你
well we won't but you will see amazing
好吧，我们不会但你会看到惊人的
people next week on Twitch on Thursday
周四在Twitch上的人们
[Music]
[音乐]